<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:locale="en">
    <string name="help_create_new"><![CDATA[
        <h1>Create Wallet - New</h1>
        <p>If you need a new Monero Address!</p>
        <p>Enter a unique wallet name and password.
        The password is used for securing your wallet data on the device. Use a strong password -
        even better use a passphrase.</p>
        <h2>Note your Mnemonic Seed!</h2>
        <p>On the following screen you will find your 25-word \"Mnemonic Seed\".
        This is the only data needed to recover your wallet at a later point
        and gain full access to your funds.
        Keeping this secure and private is very important, as it gives <em>anyone</em>
        full access to your funds!</p>
        <p>If you lose your wallet password, you can still recover your wallet with the Mnemonic Seed.</p>
        <p>There is no way to recover your Mnemonic Seed, if you lose it all your funds will be lost!
        The Mnemonic Seed can also never be changed, and if it is stolen or otherwise compromised,
        you will have to move your funds to new wallet (with a new Mnemonic Seed). Therefore, it is best
        that you backup your Mnemonic Seed by writing it down and storing it in <em>multiple</em> safe
        and secure places.</p>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="help_create_seed"><![CDATA[
        <h1>Create Wallet - Seed</h1>
        <p>If you already have a Monero Address and want to recover the transactions from the blockchain!</p>
        <p>Enter a unique wallet name and password. The password is used for securing your wallet data on the device.
        Use a strong password - even better use a passphrase.</p>
        <p>Enter your Seed in the field \"Mnemonic Seed\".<p>
        <p>Enter the block number of the first transaction used for this address in the
        field \"Restore Height\". You can also use a date in the format YYYY-MM-DD. If you are not sure,
        enter an approximate date/blockheight <em>before</em> you first used this wallet address.</p>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="help_create_keys"><![CDATA[
        <h1>Create Wallet - Keys</h1>
        <p>If you are recovering your wallet using your keys!</p>
        <p>Enter a unique wallet name and password. The password is used for securing your wallet data on the device.
        Use a strong password - even better use a passphrase.<p>
        <p>Enter your Monero Address in the field \"Public Address\" and fill out \"View Key\" and  \"Spend Key\".</p>
        <p>Enter the block number of the first transaction used for this address in the
        field \"Restore Height\". You can also use a date in the format YYYY-MM-DD. If you are not sure,
        enter an approximate date/blockheight <em>before</em> you first used this wallet address.</p>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="help_create_view"><![CDATA[
        <h1>Create Wallet - View</h1>
        <p>If you just want to monitor incoming transactions to a wallet!</p>
        <p>Enter a unique wallet name and password. The password is used for securing your wallet data on the device.
        Use a strong password - even better use a passphrase.<p>
        <p>Enter your Monero Address in the field \"Public Address\" and fill out the \"View Key\".</p>
        <p>Enter the block number of the first transaction used for this address in the
        field \"Restore Height\". You can also use a date in the format YYYY-MM-DD. If you are not sure,
        enter an approximate date/blockheight <em>before</em> you first used this wallet address.</p>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="help_details"><![CDATA[
        <h1>Wallet Details</h1>
        <h2>Public address</h2>
        Your public address is like your bank account number you can share this with anyone without
        having to fear losing your Monero. People will send Monero to your wallet using this address.
        <h2>Mnemonic Seed</h2>
        This is the only data needed to recover your wallet at a later point and gain full access to
        your funds. Keeping this private and secure is very important, as it gives <em>anyone</em> full
        access to your Monero! If you haven’t written this down somewhere safe please do!
        <h2>Wallet Files Recovery Password</h2>
        Make sure you write this password down. If you reset your device or uninstall the app, you
        will need it to access your wallet again.<br/>
        <h3>CrAzYpass</h3>
        If the password displayed here is 52 alphanumeric characters in groups of 4 - congratulations!
        Your wallet files are secured with a 256-bit key generated by your device&apos;s security
        features based on the passphrase you chose (on creation or by changing it). This makes it
        extremely difficult to hack!<br/>
        This feature is mandatory for all newly created wallets.
        <h3>Legacy Password</h3>
        If you see your passphrase here, your wallet files are not as secure as when using
        a CrAzYpass. To fix this, simply select \"Change Passphrase\" from the menu. After entering
        a new passphrase (maybe even the same one as before) the app will generate a CrAzYpass for
        you and secure your wallet files with it. Write it down!
        <h3>CrAzYpass wallets</h3>
        If you ever need to reinstall Monerujo (for example after resetting your phone or switching
        to a new one) or you want to use your wallet files on a different device or PC, you have to
        use this Recovery Password in order to access your wallet again.<br/>
        By selecting \"Change Passphrase\" from the menu, you can choose another passphrase. Beware
        that this will generate a new Recovery Password. Write it down!
        <h2>View key</h2>
        Your view key can be used to monitor incoming transactions to your wallet without giving
        permission to spend the funds inside your wallet.
        <h2>Spend key</h2>
        Your spend key allows anyone to spend the Monero associated with your wallet, so don’t tell
        anyone this key, keep it safe like your Mnemonic Seed.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="help_list"><![CDATA[
        <h1>Sidekick</h1>
        This is the sidekick app. It should ideally be used on a phone that is not connected
        to the internet. As long as that condition is true, it\'s almost as secure as a hardware wallet.
        If we take into account that you don\'t have to purchase a dedicated crypto device, it could be
        considered more secure: nobody knows you\'re using this.

        To set it up, you\'ll need another phone with the monerujo app installed and connect both phones
        via Bluetooth:
        <ol>
        <li>Turn on Bluetooth on both phones</li>
        <li>Go to the Bluetooth settings on the monerujo phone and pair it with this one</li>
        <li>Open both sidekick and monerujo apps</li>
        </ol>

        <h2>Creating a new sidekick wallet</h2>
        <h3>On sidekick:</h3>
        Click on the + button to create a new wallet.

        Pick a name you like for the wallet. We suggest something that will help you match it with its corresponding wallet on the monerujo phone, for example use the same wallet name on both.

        Enter a desired password. Try to make it a good one, it\'s what\'s needed to use the wallet.

        Write down the seed just like with any normal wallet. Please don\'t skip this step, it\'s the key to recover your funds.

        Open your newly created wallet. Go to the monerujo phone.

        <h3>On monerujo:</h3>
        Click on the "Connect to sidekick" menu or icon. You should see the sidekick phone\'s name in the list, pick it.

        If it\'s successfully connected, when you press the + button you should only have one option: "Restore from sidekick".

        Pick a name for the wallet on this phone. Same advice as before applies.

        You\'ll notice that there\'s no seed displayed here. Good. That\'s the whole point.

        Once you proceed, this new wallet should appear on the main screen just like a normal wallet.

        <h2>Using your sidekick wallet</h2>
        Check that both phones are connected via Bluetooth and both apps are opened.

        <h3>On sidekick:</h3>
        Open your wallet of choice.

        <h3>On monerujo:</h3>
        Connect to sidekick.

        Open the wallet matching the one you have opened on the sidekick phone.

        Use it as you\'d normally use any wallet. Let it scan to see incoming transactions, share addresses, or send moneros. If the app needs to do something that involves your keys, it\'ll ask for permission from sidekick.

        <h3>On sidekick:</h3>
        If monerujo requested permission, you should see a dialog that shows the transaction details like amount and fees. You\'ll also see two options, to ACCEPT or DENY it. Choose wisely.

        <h3>On monerujo:</h3>
        The transaction should be signed and ready to be sent. Press to make it so.
         <br/>
    ]]></string>

    <string name="help_ok">Got it!</string> <!-- Note: "Got it" as in "I understand this" -->
</resources>
